[
    {
        "question": "What is the most populated U.K. city after London?",
        "answer": "Birmingham -- Located in England`s west Midlands, it has 2.93 million inhabitants as of 2019. London`s population is 9 million."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which English city is closest to the famous Stonehenge monument?",
        "answer": "Salisbury -- Located in southern England, It is just 10 minutes away."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is directly south of Georgia?",
        "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which four US states share a border with Texas?",
        "answer": "Arkansas, Louisiana, New Mexico, Oklahoma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Silver State`?",
        "answer": "Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who explored the Hudson River in 1609?",
        "answer": "Henry Hudson"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the world famous La Scala opera house?",
        "answer": "Milan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is nicknamed the `Crossroads of the West`?",
        "answer": "Salt Lake City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is nicknamed `Beantown`?",
        "answer": "Boston"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two US states share a border with Delaware?",
        "answer": "Maryland and Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Times Square is located in what US city?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river begins at Lake Itasca?",
        "answer": "Mississippi River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Guadalcanal is located in what group of islands?",
        "answer": "The Solomon Islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state can you find the `Garden of the Gods`?",
        "answer": "Colorado"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city created a new beachfront when it hosted the Olympics?",
        "answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which U.S. state was the first dinosaur skeleton found in North America?",
        "answer": "New Jersey -- A dinosaur skeleton was discovered in 1858 by William Parker Foulke in Haddonfield, New Jersey."
    },
    {
        "question": "What city was formerly known as Saigon?",
        "answer": "Ho Chi Minh City"
    },
    {
        "question": "During World War I, the territory known as South West Africa was a colony of which country?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which national capital has the coldest average temperature?",
        "answer": "Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. state produces the greatest number of Christmas trees, more specifically Douglas fir?",
        "answer": "North Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "What islands are located in the Bering Strait between Russia and Alaska?",
        "answer": "Diomede Islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second largest saltwater lake in the U.S.?",
        "answer": "Lake Pontchartrain"
    },
    {
        "question": "French fries are claimed to have originated in which country?",
        "answer": "Belgium"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean does the African country, Burundi, has access to?",
        "answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after John Lennon?",
        "answer": "Liverpool"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Charles de Gaulle?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Louis Armstrong?",
        "answer": "New Orleans"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after John Foster Dulles?",
        "answer": "Washington, D.C."
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Ayatollah Khomeini?",
        "answer": "Teheran"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city named its airport after Leonardo da Vinci?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "US city Milwaukee is located on the shores of what lake?",
        "answer": "Lake Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is nicknamed the `Birthplace of the Nation`?",
        "answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kodiak Island is the largest island in which US state?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of County Kerry, Ireland?",
        "answer": "Tralee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What four US states start with the letter I?",
        "answer": "Idaho, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city had the first subway?",
        "answer": "Boston"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is Transilvania in?",
        "answer": "Romania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What four U.S. states do not allow billboards?",
        "answer": "Alaska, Hawaii, Maine, and Vermont"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country`s flag is not shape liked a rectangle?",
        "answer": "Nepal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the shorthand name for the unrecognized nation of the Pridnestrovian Moldavian Republic?",
        "answer": "Transnistria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest Australian State by land mass?",
        "answer": "Western Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main currency in Denmark?",
        "answer": "The Danish krone"
    },
    {
        "question": "The longest bridge in the world can be found in what country?",
        "answer": "In China - The Danyang-Kunshan Grand Bridge in China is no less than 102.4 miles-164.8 kilometres long."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which South American country borders both the Caribbean Sea and the Pacific Ocean?",
        "answer": "Colombia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of Liverpool, England is served by an airport named for what man?",
        "answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what county is Chicago, Illinois located?",
        "answer": "Cook County"
    },
    {
        "question": "What European country is named in honor of the Dinaric Alps and their appearance?",
        "answer": "Montenegro"
    },
    {
        "question": "The two largest islands in the Mediterranean Sea are part of what country?",
        "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is the fashion center of Italy?",
        "answer": "Milan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Kenya?",
        "answer": "Nairobi"
    }
]